"迷失" 前情提要...
Previously on "Lost"...
- 这儿刻了一堆名字 Jacob在哪?  - 我不知道
- There are names. Where's Jacob?  - I don't know.
- 为什么我的名字 会写在这上面?  - 他没告诉我
- Why is my name written down on this thing?  - He didn't tell me.
- 他想从我这儿得到什么?  - 我得确保把你和Jack一起
- What does he want from me?  - I had to get you and Jack
- 从神庙那儿叫过来  - 什么? 为什么?
- as far away from that temple as I possibly could.  - What? Why?
因为有人马上就要去那儿了
'Cause someone's coming there.
很坏的人
Someone bad.
- 要走还来得及  - 我不走
- There's still time.  - Not for me.
- 喔!  - 哦!
- Whoa!  - Oh!
Jarrah在哪?
Where's Jarrah?
我没事 谢谢
I'm fine. Thank you.
- 他在哪?!  - 他刚刚杀了Dogen
- Where is he?!  - Considering that he just killed Dogen,
- 我想他不会乐意和我们凑成堆  - Dogen是谁?
- I don't think he's gonna be joining us.  - Who's Dogen?
- 寺庙里主事的那个人  - Sayid把翻译官也杀了
- The guy in charge of the temple.  - Sayid killed the interpreter, too.
- 你没搞错吧?  - 他站在他们的尸体旁
- Are you sure?  - He was standing over their dead bodies
手里拿着把血淋淋的匕首 所以 嗯 我确定无疑
holding a bloody dagger, so, yeah, I'm pretty sure.
你之前还说躲在寺庙里很安全
You said we were safe at the temple.
- 别人也是这么跟我说的  - 呃 海滩那边怎样了?
- That's what I was told.  - Well, what about the beach?
- 什么海滩?  - 我们埋了Locke的那个海滩 他们住过的那个海滩
- What beach?  - Where we buried Locke, where they lived.
至少在那儿 我们还能弄到水
At least we'll have the water at our backs,
而且地形也熟悉 还有人有更好的建议么?
and it's familiar territory. Anybody else got a better idea?
- 没 就去海滩吧  - 走那边
- No. The beach it is.  - That way.
走吧
Move.
... 就是在这座岛上 命运发生了转变
... and it was on this island that everything changed,
最终尘埃落定...
that everything finally became clear...
厄尔巴岛...
Elba...
正是拿破仑东山再起的发源地
is where Napoleon faced his greatest task.
因为他最悲惨的下场 不是受到流放
Because exile wasn't the worst of his fate.
真正让他无法忍受的 是权力的剥夺
What was truly devastating to him was the loss of his power.
当然 他们允许他保留皇帝的头衔
Sure, they allowed him to keep the title of Emperor.
然而有名无实 毫无意义
But without any power, it was meaningless.
他还不如死了更痛快
He might just as well have been dead.
好吧 记得 明天五六节课我们继续 谢谢
All right, remember, five and six tomorrow. Thank you.
Reynolds校长 上午好
Principal Reynolds. Good morning.
跟我来
Walk with me.
Linus 轮值表稍微调整了下
Linus, there's been a slight schedule shift.
今天放学后
I'm going to need you to supervise detention
- 你去监管那些留堂生  - 什么?
- after school today.  - What?
确切说 这周每天都是你
In fact, all week.
裁员 资金周转不灵 还有许多你不了解的麻烦事
Cutbacks, budget crises, events above your pay grade.
毫无疑问 我们一个人得当两个用
Needless to say, some of us have to pull double duty.
但今天历史社团有活动啊
But we have history club today.
- 孩子们等着我呢...  - 历史社团只有5个学生 Linus
- Those kids need me...  - There are five students in history club, Linus.
- 少了你 他们不会死的  - 我们不能找个 更胜任此事的人么?
- They'll live.  - Shouldn't we be encouraging the ones with ambition?
得了吧 那个社团对他们来说无所谓 但对你不同
Spare me. The club isn't for them. It's for you.
这让你有被需求感
It makes you feel needed.
不幸的是 现在留堂生真的需要你
Unfortunately for now, you're needed in detention.
多谢配合 Linus
Thanks for your understanding, Linus.
其实 你该叫我Linus博士
It's Dr. Linus, actually.
哦 我可爱的... 毁了!
Oh, for the love of... It's ruined!
- 全毁了! 哦!  - 出... 什么事了 Leslie?
- It's ruined! Ohh!  - What's... what's the problem, Leslie?
哦 福尔马林 沾到... 福尔马林了
Oh, formaldehyde. For... formaldehyde's the problem.
你知道有什么能洗掉福尔马林么? 没有
You know what gets out formaldehyde? Nothin'.
要是我有件实验室工作服
Maybe if I had some frickin' lab aprons,
我就不用因为班上那些废物
I wouldn't have to pay for our incompetent students
再跑去Marshalls 买过一件衣服了
with another trip to Marshalls.
- 都是为了减少预算  - Reynolds难道就不能为了
- Budget cutbacks.  - How hard would it be for Reynolds
科学知识的传播 稍微放点儿血么?
to spread around a little of the love to the sciences?
我从上个世纪五十年代开始 就跟实验器材打交道
You know. I'm dealing with lab equipment in there from the 1950s.
- 他干嘛搞成这样?  - Reynolds校长说了算
- Now why is that?  - Principal Reynolds is an administrator.
他不是老师 他早忘了
He's not a teacher. He's forgotten what
公立学校是啥体制的了
the public school system is about.
嗯 作为啥狗屁养老金的交换条件 暑假不放假
Yeah, summers off in exchange for a crap pension.
我得记得提醒他
I'm happy to remind him.
不 照顾好孩子 这才是关键
No, taking care of the kids. That's what's important.
好啦 你还一门心思在教学啊
Okay. You just keep dreamin'.
哦 我知道你已经不搭理这一套了 但... 我不会放弃的
Oh, I know you've given up, but... I refuse to.
或许你才配当校长
Maybe you should be the principal.
别人也这么说
So says the substitute.
我才配当校长 你为什么这么说呢?
What do you mean, I should be the principal?
听上去 你很在乎这所学校
It just sounds like you care about this place.
如果现任校长不在乎
And if the man in charge doesn't,
那就到该换人的时候了
then maybe it's time for a change.
我同意你的看法 但谁会听我的?
I appreciate the sentiment, but who's gonna listen to me?
我就听着呢
I'm listenin'.
不如你告诉我 回那儿去的东西是什么?
How about you tell me what that thing back there was?
- 那东西在雕像后杀了她的朋友  - 还杀了Jacob 对么?
- That thing's what killed her friends back at the statue.  - And Jacob, right?
它也杀了Jacob
It killed Jacob, too.
嗯 当然 还杀了Jacob
Yeah, of course. And Jacob.
当然
Of course.
你叫Miles 对么?
You're Miles, right?
全名Miles Straume?
Miles Straume?
你可以和死者谈话
You communicate with the dead.
准确地说 不行 我...
Not technically. I...
我可以告诉你 人是怎么死的
I can tell you how someone died,
分辨出他们死前的最后一丝想法
pick up their last thoughts before they check out,
但我需要靠近他们的身边
but I need to be near their bodies.
这是从Jacob身上掉下来的
This is what's left of Jacob's body.
那么告诉我 Miles 他是怎么死的?
So tell me, Miles, how did he die?
Linus杀了他
Linus killed him.
什么?
What?
他瞎说
That's not true.
你确定?
Are you sure?
呃 他站在Jacob尸体旁边
Well, he was standing over Jacob's dead body
手上还拿着把血淋淋的匕首 所以... 嗯 我很确定
with a bloody dagger, so... yeah, I'm pretty sure.
谢谢
Thank you.
Jacob对我来说 就像爸爸一样
Jacob was the closest thing I ever had to a father.
啊哦
Uh-oh.
迷失 第6季第7集
我要找些工具
I'm gonna look for some tools
把住的地方收拾出来
and get to work on some shelter.
剩下的人 看看还有什么能吃的 或者生个火
The rest of you, see what food's left, maybe get a fire going.
对哦 生火可以搞定一切
Yeah, a fire'll fix everything.
你要我做些什么吗?
Is there anything you'd like me to do?
通灵这玩意儿... 太不靠谱了
You know, psychics... totally unreliable.
Miles还想敲诈我...
Miles actually tried to blackmail me once into...
你很会交朋友嘛 啊?
You make friends easy, don't ya?
啊 啊
Ah. Ah.
除此之外 他们还要再得
And on top of that, they'll have to convert
两分才能扳平比分
on a 2-point conversion to make it a tie game.
我给你做了顿火鸡大餐
I made you one of the turkey meals
用了你喜欢的红莓果酱哦
with the cranberry sauce that you like.
又是一顿营养均衡的大餐吧?
It ain't one of them "lean" deals, is it?
是的 爸爸 这是有机食品
No. Dad. It's organic.
我想让你保持身体健康
I'm trying to keep you healthy.
貌似有点晚了吧
Well, it's a little too late for that.
工作怎么样啊?
How was work?
我有着近代欧洲史的博士学位...
I have a doctorate in modern European history...
却被派去监管那些留堂生
And yet I'm babysitting burnouts in detention.
留堂生 嗯?
Detention, huh?
最糟的是
And the worst of it is,
当我看着那些派给我监管的
as I look out at those ingrates
混账学生时...
that I'm tasked with watching...
我不由自主地想...
I can't help thinking...
或许我还及不上他们中任何一个人
that maybe I'm more a loser than any of them.
我真不希望看到你过着这样的日子 Ben
This isn't the life I wanted for you, Ben.
我希望你能有更好的生活
I wanted so much more.
我知道
I know.
所以我才会去报名参加了那个该死的达摩组织
That's why I signed up for that damn Dharma Initiative
还带了你去那个岛 还...
and took you to the island, and...
他们都是些正直的人...
They were decent people...
都比我聪明
Smarter than I'll ever be.
想想如果我们留下来的话
Imagine how different our lives would've been
生活会有多么不同
if we'd stayed.
没错 我们会一直幸福地生活下去
Yes, we'd have both lived happily ever after.
不 我是说真的 Ben
No, I'm serious, Ben.
天晓得你会变成什么样
Who knows what you would've become.
现在感觉好点了吗?
Now does that feel better?
是的
Yes.
谢谢
Thank you.
是Alex?
Alex?
Linus博士
Dr. Linus.
今天您去哪儿了? 我们迫不得已 取消了历史社团的活动
Where were you today? We had to cancel history club.
哦 对不起
Oh, I'm so sorry.
我应该在门上贴张便条的
I should've put a note on the door.
社团的活动要延期了
The club meetings have to be postponed.
这个星期我都得去留堂生那儿
I'm in detention all week.
哦 是吗? 您去做什么?
Oh, yeah? What'd you do?
Reynolds校长让我去监管 所以...
Principal Reynolds needs me to cover, so...
这周五有大学预修课程考试
A.P. Test this Friday.
我还... 指望您能来辅导一下呢
I was... kinda counting on the tutoring.
那好 你看这样如何?
All right, how about this?
明早七点 图书馆见
Tomorrow morning, 7:00 a.m. In the library.
带咖啡来哦
And you bring the coffee.
谢谢
Thanks.
天啊 您真是个大好人 Linus博士
God, you're the best, Dr. Linus.
- 别客气 Alex  - 好的
- My pleasure, Alex.  - Okay.
再见
See you.
打扰一下 我们要在这儿待多久啊?
Excuse me. How long are we going to stay here?
我跟你说过 我还不知道
I told you. I don't know yet.
我要去找我的丈夫
I need to find my husband.
相信我 如果说有人想找到他的话 那肯定是我
Trust me, if anyone wants to find him, it's me.
但我现在也全无头绪
But I don't know where to look.
你为什么想找到Jin啊?
Why do you want to find Jin?
因为你姓Kwon
Because your last name is Kwon.
他也是
So is his.
我不知道是不是
And I don't know whether
该来保护你 或他 或者你们两个
I'm supposed to protect you, him or both of you.
保护我们? 你在说些什么啊?
Protect us? What are you talking about?
你们是...
You're candidates...
接替Jacob的候选人
to replace Jacob.
接替他?
Replace him?
去干什么啊?
To do what?
如果你当了接班人 那你肯定会知道的
If you're the one selected, I imagine you'll find out.
等等 你说接班人
Wait. You said candidates.
一共有多少人啊?
How many are there?
六个
Six.
现在只剩下六个了
There are only six left.
奶酪块
Cheese curds.
Hurley啊
Hurley.
快点 醒醒啊
Come on. Wake up.
快 我们走
Come on. Let's go.
我们可以在傍晚到寺庙那儿
We can make the temple by nightfall.
我饿啦 我们... 先吃点早饭吧
I'm hungry. Let's... eat breakfast first.
不 我们可以在路上吃
No, we can eat on the way.
着什么急啊?
What's the rush?
我们可以慢慢来啊?
You know, maybe we should take our time?
为什么?
Why?
因为...
Because...
我要走了 Hurley 你走不走啊?
I'm leaving, Hurley. You coming or not?
错啦 哥们
Unh-unh, dude.
走这边
It's this way.
不 我们是从这儿来的
No, we came this way.
没错 但我们犯了个错误 走这边更快
Yeah, but that was a mistake. This is faster.
相信我 就在附近 这儿是捷径啊
Trust me, it's just around here. It's a shortcut.
- 不 不是  - 你们都错了
- No, it's not.  - You're both wrong.
去寺庙是走这条路的
Temple's that way.
你从哪儿来的?
Where did you come from?
如果我跟你说了 你肯定不会相信的
You wouldn't believe me if I told you.
- 说说看啊  - 还没到时候
- Try me.  - Not yet.
如果你想去寺庙 那就走这边
If you wanna go to the temple, it's this way.
兄弟 你相信那家伙?
Dude, you trust that guy?
至少他没有拖延时间
At least he's not stalling.
当你翻完那些书
When you're finished in that library,
就帮我搬些木材过来
give me a hand getting some more firewood.
我是在找能用的东西
Just looking for something useful.
天啊
God.
这就是人们旅行时该带的东西...
The things people will bring on a trip...
"大洋航空"
"Oceanic."
我清楚地记得飞机失事那天
I remember that plane breaking in half，
就像发生在昨天一样
like it was yesterday.
你很怀旧啊
You sound nostalgic.
也许是吧
Maybe I am.
跟你说 我本应该驾驶那次航班的
You know, I was supposed to be flying it.
815次大洋航班
Oceanic 815.
那为什么你没飞?
And why didn't you?
我睡过头了
I overslept.
- 别扯了 - 你相信吗?
- Come on. - Can you believe it?
想象下 如果闹钟没坏
Imagine how different my life would be
我的生活会有多大变化
had that alarm gone off.
能有多大变化呢?
How different would it have been?
你最终还是到这岛上来了 不是吗?
The island still got you in the end, didn't it?
走
Walk.
好 等一等
Okay, wait.
- 你不必这样做的...  - 停下
- You don't have to do this if...  - Stop.
脸朝地上趴着
On the ground. Face down.
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
听着 如果是因为Miles说的那些...
Look, if this is about at Miles said...
- 捡起来  - 什么?
- Pick it up.  - What?
捡起来 开始挖
Pick it up and start digging.
挖什么?
Dig what?
坟墓
A grave.
给谁?
For who?
你杀了Jacob
You murdered Jacob.
给你自己挖坟墓
It's for you.
第19章 东印度贸易公司
你知道答案的 我知道你能行
Now you know this. I know you do.
Cornwallis勋爵做了总督后 权利大增
Expanded Lord Cornwallis' powers as governor-general.
非常好
Very good.
现在复习1813法案
Now moving on to the Charter Act of 1813.
在制定这项法案时
At the time of the Charter,
东印度公司的权力
the East India Trading Company's power
扩张到整个印度 除了...
extended to all of India except for...
呃...
Uh...
我不知道!
I don't know!
没关系 只是小测试而已
It's okay. It's okay. It's just a test.
只是小测试?
Just a test?
这关于到我的一生 Linus博士
It's only my entire life, Dr. Linus.
- Alex 我觉得你把这件事 看得太重要了一点  - 是吗?
- Alex, I think you're being a bit overdramatic.  - Am I?
我妈妈为了付房租 兼职两份工作
My mom works two jobs just to pay our rent.
我怎么交得起大学学费 更别提是耶鲁大学?
How am I gonna pay for college, let alone Yale?
假设我有机会被录取的话
Assuming I can even get in.
你是我所有学生中 最聪明的一个
You're one of the brightest students I've ever had.
你前程似锦 毋庸置疑
I don't worry about your future at all.
真的吗?
Really?
真的 我能帮你什么?
Really. Now what can I do to help?
我给你写封推荐信 我会...
I'll write you a great letter of recommendation. I'll...
不 我需要耶鲁大学的学生 来写推荐信
No, I need someone who went there.
不幸的是 我认识的唯一一个人
Unfortunately, the only one I know
就是那头色狼 Reynolds校长
is that pervert, Principal Reynolds.
什么? "色狼"?
Excuse me? "Pervert"?
别往心里去
Forget I said that.
我只是气糊涂了
I was just angry.
Alex Reynolds校长...
Alex, has Principal Reynolds...
对你做过什么吗?
Done something to you?
什么?
What?
啊!
Ew!
不是 我发誓 不是那样的
No, I swear. It's not that.
那是什么?
Then what is it?
Linus博士 如果我告诉你
Dr. Linus, if I tell you,
你能保证不和别人说吗?
will you promise to keep it between us?
当然 我发誓
Of course I promise.
好吧
Okay.
几个月前 在校医室
So I was in the nurse's office a few months ago.
因为肚子痛
I had a stomachache,
我去了那里 后来就在床上睡着了
and I just went in to find a cot and I fell asleep.
放学后才醒
When I woke up after school,
我听到Reynolds校长在隔壁房间
In the other room, Principal Reynolds was there.
而那位校医... 我想她是忘记我还在了
And the nurse... Well, I guess she forgot I was in there.
他们在...
They were...
你知道的 做那种事
you know, doing it
在我隔壁房间
in the room right next to me,
就是给学生测听力的那间房
where they give kids hearing tests.
- 这事很恶心吧?  - 真是恶心
- Isn't that totally gross?  - Totally.
Linus博士 你不会说出去 对吧?
Dr. Linus, you're not gonna say something, are you?
不会 言出必行
No, no. A promise is a promise.
好吧 我们继续复习公海这个知识点吧?
Well, shall we return to the high seas?
嗯
Yeah.
好
Sure.
你不是想累死在挖坑前线吧?
Not exactly tearing up on the digging front, are you?
我不着急
I'm not in a big hurry.
给你带了点吃的
Brought you some grub.
希望你会喜欢吃青豆和香蕉
Hope you like green beans and banana,
因为只有这些
'cause it's all we got.
我不饿
I'm not really hungry.
随你的便
Suit yourself.
Miles 你记得你向我要过320万美元吗?
Miles, do you remember once you asked me for $3.2 million?
你还想要吗?
Do you still want it?
你准备做什么?
What are you gonna do?
你要在我的香蕉叶上开支票?
You're gonna write me a check on this banana leaf?
我要离开这座岛 当我离开后
I can get off this island, and when I do,
我关系网和人脉很广
I have a vast network of people and resources
那时候就能把那笔钱给你
that will get you that money.
你要做的 就是放了我
All you have to do is cut me loose.
有价值八百万的钻石
Why would I need your money when there are
跟那两个叫Nikki和Paulo的家伙 一起埋在这儿
a couple of jabonies under there named Nikki and Paulo
我为什么还要你的钱?
who got buried alive with $8 million in diamonds on top of them?
简直不敢相信
I can't believe you're just gonna stand by
你居然袖手旁观
and watch this happen.
Ilana要杀了我...
Ilana's gonna murder me for killing Jacob...
就因为我杀了一个不在乎生死的Jacob
a man who didn't even care about being killed.
不 他在乎
No, he cared.
- 你说什么?  - 就在你的刀
- Excuse me?  - Right up until
要插入他心脏的那一秒
the second the knife went through his heart,
他希望这一切都是误会
he was hoping he was wrong about you.
我觉得他不想死
I guess he wasn't.
继续挖!
Dig!
所以... 你没穿越时空?
So... you're not time traveling?
没有
No.
但你看起来跟30年前一样
But you look the same as you did 30 years ago.
- 这怎么可能?  - 说来话长
- How is that possible?  - Not easy to explain.
就像"终结者"似的?
Is this like a "terminator" thing?
你是个生化人?
You a cyborg?
不 我不是生化人
No, I'm not a cyborg.
- 吸血鬼?  - 是Jacob赋予我的能力
- Vampire?  - Jacob gave me a gift.
是Jacob啊 你知道他的事吗?
Jacob. What do you know about him?
我知道他死了
I know he's dead.
哥们儿 你之前说去寺庙啊
I thought you said we were going to the temple, dude.
我撒谎了
I lied.
- 为什么?  - 因为寺庙里的每一个人都死了
- Why?  - Because everyone at the temple is dead.
什么叫他们都死了?
What do you mean, they're all dead?
发生什么事了?
What happened?
我... 我不清楚发生了什么
I'm... I'm not sure what happened,
但... 我刚打那儿来
but... I just came from there,
那儿没有生还者
and there's no survivors.
我们的朋友呢? Sayid和Kate
What about our friends? Sayid, Kate.
他们... 他们不在那儿
They... they weren't there.
他们可能逃过了一劫
Maybe they made it out alive.
我只知道 不管你想在寺庙找什么...
All I know is whatever you're looking for at the temple...
那儿没有
it's not there.
你不想回那里去 原来你知道这件事?
You didn't want to go back there. Did you know about this?
Jacob曾暗示过
Jacob kinda sorta hinted at it.
你跟Jacob说过话?
You spoke to Jacob?
对啊
Yeah.
好吧 无论他说什么 别相信他
Well, whatever he said, don't believe him.
- 你去哪儿?  - 我有事情要做
- Where you going?  - There's something I need to do.
去干嘛?
To do what?
去死
Die.
嘿 有时间吗?
Hey, do you have a minute?
我想有吧 也许我可以全给他们不及格
Yes, I guess. Might as well just give 'em all F's.
告诉我 动物的属和种
Tell me, how hard is it
有那么难区分吗?
to learn the difference between a genus and a species?
你想干嘛?
What do you want?
你玩电脑很在行 是吗?
You're pretty good with computers, aren't you?
如果你不知道
Something tells me you wouldn't even be standing here
你就不会平白无故地站在这里问我
if you didn't already know that I was.
假设 你能
Could you, hypothetically,
偷偷地打开别人的邮箱吗?
access someone's E-mail account without their knowledge?
我... 可以 看是什么样的邮箱
I... yeah, it depends on the account.
员工邮箱
Say a faculty account.
假设是
Hypothetically.
- 谁的?  - Kondracki护士的
- Whose?  - Nurse Kondracki.
Kim吗? 为什么? 你觉得她很辣?
Kim? Why? Do you got the hots for her?
不 我只是...
No. I'm just...
我只是对她的信件好奇
I'm curious about some of her correspondence.
跟谁的信?
With whom?
好吧 算了
Okay. That's fine.
我没找你 是你找上的我
I didn't come to see you. You came to see me.
我没时间回答你的问题
I don't have time to play 20 questions.
你要不就告诉我 你在做什么
Now you can either tell me what it is that you're doing,
- 要不就让我安安静静地改作业  - 好吧 好吧
- or you can let me finish grading my papers in peace.  - All right, all right.
我有理由相信 她也许
I have reason to believe that she might be engaged
跟Reynolds校长有
in an inappropriate personal relationship
不正当的关系
with Principal Reynolds.
你有预谋的
You're making a play.
你在预谋件大事 对吗?
You're going after the big job, aren't you?
Leslie 你要不要帮我?
Are you going to help me or not, Leslie?
我想要个好位子
I want a good spot.
你说什么?
I'm sorry?
我想要Lamr在主停车场的停车位...
I want Lamr's spot in the main parking lot...
在枫树旁边的那个
the one next to the maple tree.
不是在枫树下边的... 是在旁边的那个
Not under the maple tree... next to the maple tree.
这样的话 我的车会在树荫底下
That way, I get the shade from the maple tree
但那些树渣子又不会掉到我车上
but not all that tree crap all over the hood of my car.
我还想要实验服 很多实验服
And I want aprons. I want lots of aprons.
我还想要一些
And I want some lab equipment in here
- 近十年的实验器材 成交吗?  - 成交
- that was built in this decade. Is that a deal?  - Deal.
你知道 你真的能让我解决那个混蛋
You know, you really had me fooled with that sweater vest.
Linus 你才是真正的杀手
Linus, you're a real killer.
之前来过这儿?
Been here before?
是的
Yes.
我在岛上这么久
And in all the time that I've spent on this island,
今天是第一次回来这里
today is the first time I've ever come back.
Jack? 哥们儿 你在哪儿?
Jack? Dude, where are ya?
我在这儿
I'm in here.
别打开 那是甘油炸药
Do not open that. There's dynamite in there.
- 那个极不稳定  - 我知道
- It's mega-unstable.  - I know.
Arzt博士就是这样...
So did Dr. Arzt...
两天后 我才把粉身碎骨的他 从我的衣服里清干净
Then I was wiping him out of my shirt two days later.
- 哥们儿 该走了  - 不 还没到时候
- Dude, it's time to go.  - No, not yet.
他想打开那根甘油炸药
He's opening up a crate of dynamite,
- 他还说过要自杀  - 我自杀不了
- and he said he wanted to kill himself.  - I can't kill myself.
什么?
What?
即便我想死... 相信我 我是认真的...
Even if I wanted to... and trust me, I do...
我... 我没有办法自杀
I... I can't kill myself.
这也就是为什么 我要让你们替我下手
Which is why I want you to do it for me.
你到底在说些什么?
What are you talking about?
我所说的是 Jack 就是...
What I'm talking about, Jack, is that...
好吧 Jacob碰过我
Well, Jacob touched me.
当Jacob碰了你... 呃 这就算是大礼了吧
And when Jacob touches you... well, it's considered a gift.
除非它根本不是
Except it's not a gift at all.
这是一个诅咒
It's a curse.
伙计!
Dude!
我说认真的 咱们现在该走了!
Seriously, let's go now!
为什么你想死?
Why do you want to die?
我将我...
I devoted my life...
长到你无法想象的生命...
longer than you can possibly imagine...
奉献给 那个告诉我
in service of a man who told me
无风不起浪的人
that everything was happening for a reason,
他说他有一个计划...
that he had a plan...
我也是计划当中的一部分...
A plan that I was a part of...
当时机成熟的时候 他就会告诉我前因后果
And when the time was right that he'd share it with me.
但是现在 那个人死了
And now that man's gone.
所以我为何想死?
So why do I want to die?
因为我发现 我已经失去生活的目标了
Because I just found out my entire life had no purpose.
哪怕我能亲手点燃这个炸药 它... 也不会炸的
Now if I light this myself, it... it won't work.
但是你能帮我点燃 Jack
But you can light it for me, Jack.
我会把导火线做得足够长 这样你就有时间跑出去
I made the fuse long enough so you'll have time to get out.
Jack 求你告诉我 你不想这么做
Jack, please tell me you're not actually considering this.
如果他执意去死
If he wants to die,
我们无论如何也阻止不了
there's nothing we're gonna do to stop him.
谢谢你
Thank you.
现在...
Now...
我们谈谈吧
Let's talk.
Jack! 伙计 我们得走了 他疯了 我知道他疯了
Jack! Dude, we gotta go. Guy's crazy, and I know crazy.
- Hurley 你走吧 我们不会有事的  - 兄弟 你马上会被炸死的!
- Hurley, go ahead. We'll be all right.  - Dude, you're gonna blow up!
- 我得和他谈谈 Hurley 你走吧  - 不 我不会丢下你不管的
- Gotta talk to him, Hurley. Just go.  - No, I'm not going without you.
Hurley 我不会有事的
Hurley, I'll be fine.
如果你改变主意的话 我会在 大概 一里外的地方等你
If you change your mind, I'll be, like, a mile away.
- 你应该和他走的 Jack  - 不 Richard 不 我不会走的
- You should go with him, Jack.  - No, Richard. No, I shouldn't.
不然你会死的
Then you're gonna die.
事实上 我觉得我俩都死不了
Actually, I don't think either one of us is gonna die.
你为何这么想?
What makes you think that?
我刚从灯塔来
I just came from a lighthouse
转盘上刻着我的名字
where my name was etched in wood
使得镜子
on a dial that turned a mirror
可以照出我从小到大住的 那栋房子的景象
that somehow reflected the image of the house that I grew up in.
Jacob的灯塔
Jacob's lighthouse.
他叫Hurley把我从这弄出去
He got Hurley to bring me out there
因为他想让我看见镜子里所反射的景象
because he wanted me to see what was reflected in that mirror.
基于某个原因 他想让我知道
For some reason, he wanted me to know
当我还是个孩子的时候 他就开始注视我了
that he had been watching me ever since I was a kid.
为什么?
Why?
我不知道为什么
I have no idea why.
但是我敢向你打赌 如果Jacob费了这么大力气
But I'm willing to bet you that if Jacob went to that trouble,
基于某个原因把我弄到岛上来
that he brought me to this island for a reason,
肯定不会让我跟你现在一起被炸死
and it's not to blow up sitting here with you right now.
- 你在拿自己的命开玩笑啊 Jack  - 是的
- That's a pretty big risk you're taking, Jack.  - Yes.
- 但如果你错了怎么办?  - 我不会错的
- What if you're wrong?  - I'm not.
想再试一根吗?
Want to try another stick?
好吧 Jack
All right, Jack.
你好像看破一切玄机了 那么... 现在该怎么办?
You seem to have all the answers. So... so now what?
我们重回起点吧
We go back to where we started.
你好 Ben
Hello, Ben.
你在这儿做什么呢?
What are you doing here?
参观啊 你又在干什么呢?
Visiting. What are you doing?
我在自掘坟墓
I'm digging my own grave.
为什么?
Why?
因为你骗我杀了Jacob
Because you talked me into killing Jacob.
你看见那边吃芒果的那个女人了吗?
Do you see that woman over there eating a mango?
她是他的保镖 她知道我做了什么
She's his bodyguard, and she knows what I did.
你得偿所愿了 因为她要杀我
So you've got what you wanted because she's going to kill me.
我可不想要你死 Ben
I don't want you to die, Ben.
其实 我是回雕塑这儿来找你的
In fact, I went back to the statue to get you,
- 但是你已经走了  - 找我? 为了什么?
- but you'd already gone.  - Get me? For what?
我正在召集一组人离开这里
I'm gathering a group to leave this place for good.
但是一旦我们走了
But once we're gone,
岛还需要人来接管
someone's gonna need to be in charge of the island.
我?
Me?
我实在找不出比你更合适的人选
I can't think of a better man for the job.
哦 在这种情况下 可能性看上去不大吧
Well, it doesn't seem very likely, does it,
对不?
under the circumstances?
我怎么样才能离开...
How am I gonna get away from...
去另一个岛 去九头蛇站
Come to the other island, to the Hydra Station.
- 那就是我们要去的地方  - 她会跟着我的
- That's where we'll be.  - She'll come after me.
往里走200码的地方 林中空地有一棵树
200 yards inland, there's a tree in the clearing
树上架了把来福枪
with a rifle leaning up against it.
如果现在走的话 你能第一个到那儿
If you go now, you'll get there first
然后你就可以干掉她
and you'll have the drop on her.
但是千万别犹豫
But don't hesitate.
她可不会
She won't.
待会见 Ben
See you soon, Ben.
嘿!
Hey!
Reynolds校长室
进来
Come in.
Linus 我现在没有时间
Linus, I don't have time
听你抱怨那些留堂生的事
to listen to you complain about detention.
我不是为这个来的 我想让你看些东西
That's not why I'm here. I want you to read something.
好吧 如果你想让你那个小社团...
Well, if this some attempt to revive your little club...
这些是3个月内的30封邮件
Those are 30 E-mails that cover a 3-month period.
这事还真淫乱
It's pretty lascivious stuff,
如果是私房事 也就罢了
which would be fine if it was private,
但是它们好像描述的是
but they seem to describe
发生在校园的行为...
acts that took place on school property...
不知廉耻的行为
acts which, morality aside,
我想学校董事会一定会不满
I think the school board would frown on,
更别说你的妻子
not to mention your wife.
你想要什么?
What do you want?
你的职位
Your job.
你要辞职...
You're gonna resign...
原因是 比如...
for, I don't know...
一些个人理由 健康问题之类 随便你掰
personal reasons, health. Your call.
在你辞职的同时 你要向校董事会
But with your resignation, you're gonna recommend
推荐我来接替你的职位
that the school board hire me as your replacement.
讽刺的是
And the irony of all this
他们会因为对你的尊敬
is that they hold you in such esteem
而让我真的坐上这个位子
that I'll get the job.
那... 我们达成共识了吗?
So... do we have an understanding?
Linus啊...
Linus...
我能给你读一封电子邮件吗?
May I read you an E-mail?
"亲爱的Reynolds校长"
"Dear Principal Reynolds,
"如果您能为我向耶鲁大学写
"I would appreciate it if you could write
"一封推荐信 我将感激涕零
"a letter of recommendation to Yale on my behalf.
"这对我很重要
"It would mean the world to me.
致礼 Alexandra Rousseau"
Sincerely, Alexandra Rousseau."
推荐信这种事真有趣 Linus
It's a funny thing about recommendations, Linus.
它们承载着2个人的希望
They work both ways.
所以...
So...
我把这个难题抛给你
I put the ball back in your court.
你可以施展你的小手段
You can execute your little machiavellian maneuvers,
争取我的工作 坐我的办公桌
go for my job, sit at my desk.
但是 唉 不幸的副作用...
But, alas, there will be an unfortunate side effect...
我能给Rousseau小姐
I will torch Miss Rousseau
灿烂的前程
and her future.
我的职位和权力 对你这么重要吗?
Is my job, my power, that important to you?
那么...
So...
你的抉择是什么 Linus博士?
What'll it be, Dr. Linus?
放下!
Drop it!
把枪放下!
Put the gun down!
你还等什么?
What are you waiting for?
我想要解释
I want to explain.
解释什么?
Explain what?
我想要解释 我知道你的感受
I want to explain that I know what you're feeling.
你不知道我的感受
You have no idea what I'm feeling.
我看着我的女儿Alex 死在我面前
I watched my daughter Alex die in front of me.
而且是我造成的
And it was my fault.
我有机会救她的
I had a chance to save her,
但是我选择了小岛...
but I chose the island...
而不是她
over her.
都是为了Jacob
All in the name of Jacob.
我为他牺牲了一切...
I sacrificed everything for him...
他甚至都不在乎
and he didn't even care.
是 我捅死了他
Yeah, I stabbed him.
我... 很生气...
I was... so angry..
昏了头
confused.
我... 我担心失去
I... I was terrified that I was about to lose
对我唯一重要的东西...
the only thing that had ever mattered to me...
权力
My power.
但是真正重要的东西...
But the thing that really mattered...
已经没了
was already gone.
很抱歉我杀了Jacob
I'm sorry that I killed Jacob.
真的
I am.
但是我也不指望你原谅我
And I do not expect you to forgive me
因为...
Because...
我不能原谅自己
I can never forgive myself.
那么你想要什么?
Then what do you want?
只要... 放我走
Just... let me leave.
你要去哪?
Where will you go?
去找Locke
To Locke.
为什么?
Why?
因为只有他能收留我
Because he's the only one that'll have me.
我会收留你
I'll have you.
Donald Lawrence Reynolds校长
Linus博士
Dr. Linus.
- 您好啊 Alex  - 我顺路来感谢Reynolds校长
- Hello, Alex.  - I was just coming by to thank Principal Reynolds.
他给我写了一封不可思议的推荐信
He wrote me the most incredible letter of recommendation.
哇 太好了
Wow. Wonderful.
是您起了作用吗?
Did you have something to do with it?
我是说 我原本以为他可能会说些好话
I mean, I thought he might say some nice things,
- 但是他好话都说绝了 - 不 跟我没关系 Alex
- but he really went all out.  - No, it wasn't me, Alex.
但是大家都说 你是个优秀的学生
But it always say you're a great student.
很明显 不只有我能看到
Obviously, I wasn't the only one who noticed.
谢谢你 博士...
Thanks, doctor...
Linus 你他妈的在我办公室里干啥呢?
Linus, what the hell are you doing in my office?
应你的要求 来送这周留堂生的
Just dropping off the detention sign-up sheet for the week,
登记表
per your request.
放我桌上就行
Just put it on my desk.
那么我们历史社团见?
So will I see you at history club?
- 啊 您是说何时重新搞活动吗?  - 哦 不 我们按原计划进行
- Uh, you mean when it's back on?  - Oh, no, we've got our old slot back.
Reynolds校长找了别人监管留堂生
Principal Reynolds found someone to cover for detention.
是不是?
Isn't that right?
是 没错
Yes, that's right.
哦 好吧 下午4点见
Well, then, see you at 4:00.
再见
Bye.
嘿 事情办成了吗?
Hey. Did you do it?
没有
No.
没有?
No?
没有?! 等等
No?! Wait.
我... 我的停车位呢?
What... what about my parking space?
你可以用我的
You can have mine.
需要帮忙吗?
Do you need a hand?
帮我弄下苫布
Please help me with the tarp.
长官 海滩上有人
Sir, there are people on the beach.
我们要停下来吗?
Should we stop?
不
No.
照计划行事
Proceed as planned.
遵命 Widmore先生
Yes, sir, Mr. Widmore.